- 왔냐?
- 안녕하세요
Hi, my name's Chandler.
I just moved in next door.
이웃에 이사 온 챈들러입니다
은하계 최후의 에너지원을 놓고
저랑 한판 붙어보는 게 어떨까요
Would you like to battle me
in a post-apocalyptic world...
for control of the galaxy's
last remaining energy source?
Sure, neighbor! Come on in!
- 물론이죠, 입장
- 그래야지
Is Janine around?
재닌은 있냐?
아니, 댄스학원 갔어
She's at dance class.
옛날 내 방 좀 구경할까?
Can I check my room?
재닌 물건은 뒤지지 마라
무지 화내더라
Don't go through her stuff.
She gets really mad.
Oh, my God!
맙소사
It's like a guy never lived in here.
한 남자의 흔적이
완전히 사라졌잖아
You gotta be careful. This girl
thing is dangerous. It's spreading.
여자들 물건은 자칫하면
사방에 널리니까 조심해라
It is?
그래?
Is this your pretty pink pillow
on the couch?
이 앙증맞은 분홍색
베개가 네 거냐?
아니
아무 것도 안 들어가는
쥐알 만한 상자가 네 거냐?
Is that your tiny little box that's
too small to put anything in?
- 아니
- 그래
Okay, this is not good.
You are a guy, okay?
이건 좋지 않아
넌 남자야, 그렇지?
여긴 남성의 공간이라고
This is a "guy's" place.
이러다 곧 손톱손질까지
하게 될 걸?
Soon, you'll be soaking
your fingers in stuff.
머리를 커다란
드라이어에 넣고...
And your head's gonna be under a big,
brown, drying, big, drying.. It's not good.
하여튼 안 좋아
-You're right. I'll talk to her.
-Talk to her. Be a man!
그래, 맞다
얘기해야겠어
얘기해야지
사내답게 굴어
- 난 사나이야!
- 싸워서 이겨!
-I'm a man.
-Defend yourself!
We have to hem the new dust ruffle.
챈들러, 새 침대보 꿰매야지
금방 갈게, 자기야
Be right there, sweetums.
Totally different situation.
전혀 다른 상황이야
The One With Ross' Teeth
Hey, guys.
얘들아
힐러리하고는
아침 잘 먹었어?
-How was breakfast with Hillary?
-Okay.
괜찮았는데 남자친구랑
깨졌다고 좀 우울하더라
She's still depressed because
she broke up with her boyfriend.
그렇구나
Is this Hillary, your
hot assistant chef, Hillary?
힐러리라면 그 새끈한
주방장보조 말인가?
그래
내가 갈 때마다
눈길 주던 여자?
The one that stares at me
when I come in?
The one who looked at you once
because you got in her way.
오빠가 길 막고 있어서
딱 한 번 쳐다봤네
Still, I could tell. She was into me.
어쨌든 나한테
관심 있는 눈치더라
Why don't you set us up?
소개시켜줄래?
Are you setting Ross up with someone?
Does she have a wedding dress?
로스한테 누구 소개하려고?
그 여자 웨딩드레스 있대?
Come on, I'm serious.
모니카, 난 진심이야
알았어, 결혼만
안 한다고 약속하면
Okay, I'll do it, but as long as
you promise you won't marry her.
Fine, I..
What if she's the one?
그래, 난...
천생연분이면 어떡하지?
Man, you have a problem.
너 진짜 중증이다
- 얘들아
- 왔니?
Rachel?
- 레이첼
- 왜?
마사지 손님들한테 돌릴
전단을 만드는데
I'm making up flyers to try
to get new massage clients.
Can I come to Bloomingdale's
and use the copier?
너희 백화점에 있는
복사기 좀 써도 되니?
Sure, but they might think it's weird
since I don't work there anymore.
난 이제 백화점 안 다니니까
사람들이 이상하게 볼 텐데?
Oh, my God! What happened?
세상에, 무슨 일 있었니?
I got a job at Ralph Lauren.
나 랄프 로렌에 취직했어
Well, that's great! Congratulations!
잘됐다, 축하해
A year ago.
1년 전에
You've lasted all year! Good for you.
1년이나 버텼네? 잘했다
You could still use the copier
where I actually work.
지금 근무하는 데 있는
복사기를 쓰면 되지
부장님한테 안 들키게
점심시간에 와
But come by at lunch
so my boss doesn't see you.
그렇지 않아도 나
미운 털 많이 박혔어
Kim will freak out.
She doesn't like me.
-I don't think my boss likes me.
-I don't think mine likes me.
우리 부장도 날 싫어하는데
나도 마찬가지야
Maybe it's a universal thing.
누구든 그렇지 않을까?
11시 반에 이렇게 노닥거리는
근무태도 때문일 수도 있겠지
Maybe because you're all hanging
around here at 11:30 on a Wednesday.
Let's head off to work.
빨리 일하러 가자
-Thank you.
-Sure.
- 고맙다
- 별말씀을
You will not believe this.
내 얘기 들으면 놀랄 걸?
I was making copies,
and Ralph Lauren came in.
한참 복사하고 있는데
랄프 로렌이 들어오더라
Oh, my God. Did you talk to him?
세상에, 얘기해봤어?
A little. He seems really nice.
그럼, 잠깐이었지만
좋은 사람 같더라
-Good kisser.
-What?
- 키스도 잘하고
- 뭐?
What?
뭐야?
- 그 사람이랑 키스했어?
- 아무렴
-You kissed him?
-Totally.
Phoebe, are you serious?
피비, 정말이야?
그래, 들어와서 자기소개하고
다음 순간 일 터졌지 뭐
He came in and introduced himself.
The next thing I know,
we're making out!
Phoebe, you do know he's married?
피비, 그 사람
유부남인 거 아니?
몰라
Phoebe.
피비...
I'm supposed to ask every guy
I make out with if he's married?
그럼 키스할 때마다
유부남인지 물어보라고?
No, yeah, I should.
물론 그래야지
Hey, Joey.
- 안녕, 조이
- 그래요
Can I talk to you for a second?
There's a kid in this picture.
잠깐 얘기 좀 하죠
저 아이 말인데요
혹시 무슨 친척이라도 되나요?
Do you know this kid?
Is it a relative?
No. I just thought it was cute.
아뇨, 그냥 예뻐서요
That's what I was afraid of. Okay....
역시 우려하던 대로군
I really want you to feel
at home here, but...
나도 그쪽이 여기서
편하게 지냈으면 하지만
some of this new stuff,
it's too girlie.
어떤 물건들은
너무 여성취향이에요
Like what?
뭐가요?
Like this.
Pictures of cute babies we don't know.
이런 거요, 우리도
잘 모르는 아기 사진
We can't have that.
난 이런 거 안 키워요
Joey, it's Anne Geddes.
She's a famous artist.
조이, 앤 게디스라고
유명한 사진작가예요
난 이 아기 몰라요
I don't know this baby. I don't know
if she's a famous artist or not.
유명한 작가인지는
더더욱 모르고
유세를 부리는 건 아니지만
I don't want to be a jerk, but
you're changing too much around here.
분위기가 너무 변했잖아요
미안해요, 난 그냥 좀더
멋지고 꾸며보고 싶어서
I'm sorry. I wanted to make
the place a little nicer.
그건 알지만 좀 지나쳐요
But it's too much stuff.
양초에다...
You know, you got the candles and
the "foofy schmoofer" thing here.
여긴 야리꾸리한 거시기
Over here, you got
a picture of a watering can.
벽에는 물뿌리개 그림까지
I just thought..
- 하지만 그건.....
- 물론 유명한 물뿌리개겠죠
I'm sure it's a famous watering can.
But come on.
그리고 화장실에 있는
뜨거운 작대기는 뭐죠?
And what is with the really hot stick
in the bathroom?
It's a curling iron.
머리 마는 기구예요
그렇다면 할 수 없고
Well, that's okay then.
좋아요, 가령 내 수건!
내가 욕실에 들어가면
Okay, my towels, for instance.
I come into the bathroom...
and my towel is not on the floor,
where I keep it.
원래 보관 장소인
바닥에 없어요
It's up here on some hook.
And it smells different.
여기 걸려있죠
웬 갈고리에
- 냄새도 다르고
- 깨끗하잖아요
-It's clean.
-It feels different.
하지만 느낌이 다르죠
잘 말렸으니까요
It's dry.
All right, I can make my peace
with the clean, dry towels.
좋아요, 깨끗하게 잘 말린
수건은 내가 참죠
그건 그렇다 치고
이 부스러기는 뭐요
Also what is with
these chips you bought?
아니, 그건 포푸리예요
먹지 말고 향기를 맡아요
It's potpourri.
You're supposed to smell it.
Well, that's like summer in a bowl.
벌써 여름이 느껴지네요
부장님, 안녕하세요
Kim, hi.
I handed in that marketing report, and
I never got to hear what you thought.
제가 마케팅 보고서 올렸는데
아직 아무 말씀이 없으시네요
I didn't read it.
안 읽어봤어
봄 상품이군요
올해는 굉장하겠죠?
The spring line's really gonna be
great this year, huh?
그래
I hear Ralph Lauren fooled around
with someone in the copy room.
회장님이 복사실에서 누구랑
이상한 행동을 하셨다던데
Tell me everything.
자세히 들어볼까?
Hey, guys.
- 안녕, 얘들아
- 어서 와
What's up?
별일 없지?
You know....
저런, 맙소사다
Oh, my God.
What happened to your teeth?
이가 왜 그래?
I whitened them.
표백했지
Really?
진짜?
What do you think?
어때 보여?
눈이 부셔서 똑바로 못 보겠어
I think I shouldn't look
directly at them.
Come on, seriously.
어허, 장난하지 말고
너무나 지나치게 하얗다
-They're really, really, really white.
-What was wrong with your old...
옛날의 그 인간적인
치아는 어디 갔냐?
human teeth?
I did leave the gel on
a little longer than it said to.
젤을 약간 오래
바르고 있었더니 이래
-How much longer?
-A day.
얼마나 오래 뒀는데?
하루
Tonight is your date with Hillary.
오늘밤에 힐러리랑
데이트 있는 거 알지?
알아, 그래서 한 거야
진짜로 보기 안 좋아?
I know. That's why I did it.
Are they really that bad?
아니, 뭐 괜찮다
You'll be fine.
Hillary's blind, right?
힐러리 장님 맞지?
She will be after tonight.
- 내일부터 장님 될 거야
- 그렇지
Oh, Rach.
Do you notice anything..?
저기, 레이첼
나 뭐 달라진 거...
Your teeth?
Yes, I saw them from outside.
그 이빨? 밖에서도 보이더라
너희는 믿지 못하겠지만
You guys are never gonna
believe this...
but Phoebe made out
with Ralph Lauren.
피비가 랄프 로렌이랑
입을 맞췄단다
- 뭐?
- 세상에
-What?
-Oh, my God!
회사에서 두 사람이 우연히
만나 키스를 한 거야
She ran into him at my office,
and they just made out.
The craziest thing is,
now my boss likes me because...
이 충격적인 소식을 전해줬더니
이젠 부장님이 날 예뻐하시더라
it's the best gossip
she's heard all year.
오늘은 내 친구들이
너무나 자랑스럽다
I am proud of all my friends today.
I can't believe Phoebe made out
with Ralph Lauren.
피비가 랄프 로렌하고
키스를 하다니
I'm so jealous!
샘나 죽겠다
Hi, I'm Chandler,
your live-in boyfriend.
함께 사는 그대의 연인
챈들러 문안드리옵니다
Chandler, please. Come on.
넌 잘 모르는구나
Look at him.
이걸 좀 봐
Well, I am no woman,
but that is one tasty dish.
내가 여자는 아니지만
구미가 확 당기네
얘들아
Here.
- 받으시고
- 그래
Who's the silver fox?
이 은발의 미남은 누구야?
That is your make-out buddy.
Don't you recognize him?
네가 입 맞춘 남자란다
몰라보겠니?
Oh, wait.
피비, 사랑해요
키스해줘요
"Phoebe, I love you.
Kiss me, please."
That's not Ralph Lauren.
It sounds like him, though.
이 사람 랄프 로렌 아냐
말투는 비슷하지만
-What?
-Ralph doesn't look like that guy.
뭐?
그래, 랄프는 이렇게 안 생겼어
He's young, and he's got long hair
and a beard and a Hacky Sack..
젊고, 긴 머리에 턱수염
오자미를 들고 있던데
맙소사, 그건 랄프 로렌이
아니라 복사실 사환 케니야
Oh, my God. That's not Ralph Lauren.
That's Kenny the copy guy!
What?
뭐?
내가 미쳐, 부장님한테
랄프 로렌이라고 했으니
I told my boss that someone
made out with Ralph Lauren.
If she finds out that I lied to her,
she'll hate me even more. Phoebe!
그게 거짓말인 줄 알면
날 더 싫어할 텐데, 피비!
Why would the copy guy say
he's Ralph Lauren?
왜 복사실 사환이
자기 신분을 속여?
너랑 키스하려고 그랬겠지
To get you to make out with him!
This will make them look less white.
이걸 입으면 이가 좀
어둡게 보일 거야
Nope.
아니다
그니까 효과가 없는 색은
Colors that don't work are...
blue, yellow, green, red, black,
white, orange and purple.
파랑, 노랑, 초록, 빨강
검정, 흰색, 오렌지, 자주야
Do you wanna try this highlighter again?
이 치아 미백제 또 쓸래?
No, I think it poisoned me a little.
싫어, 아무래도
독성이 있나 봐
한 시간 후면 데이트인데
어떡하면 좋지?
The date starts in an hour.
What am I'm gonna do?
Maybe if your skin was lighter,
your teeth wouldn't look so bright.
그래, 피부색이
조금만 더 밝으면
치아색이 약간 죽을 텐데
Oh, great! So all I need to do
is get some new skin. Thank you.
그럼 새 피부만 이식하면
되겠구나, 고맙다
그게 아니라 메이크업을
조금만 하자고
If we put just a little bit
of makeup on you..
Whoa!
소꿉장난할 나이는 지났다
We're not 13 anymore.
This is the only thing left
that has a shot at working.
달리 뾰족한 수가 없잖아
내가 메이크업한 걸 모를까?
Won't she notice I have makeup on?
남자들 절반은 메이크업해
Half the guys out there
have makeup on.
What?
뭐?
Half the people.. I mean..
Just try it and see.
사람들의 절반이라고
일단 한 번만 해보자
싫어, 메이크업은 안 돼
I am not putting on makeup.
Hello? Ross, could you put up
some of these flyers for me?
나 왔다, 있었구나
로스, 이 전단 좀 돌려줄래?
그래
으악! 괴물! 괴물이다!
No! Demon! Demon!
Our drawers will smell nice, and
we didn't waste these pantyhose.
서랍에서 냄새도 없애고
스타킹도 활용하는 거야
속옷을 다 버리면
신이 진노하시지
God forbid we throw out old underwear.
You know what?
I'm gonna go over to Joey's.
난 조이한테 가야겠다
서랍 정리하기로 했잖아
We've got to organize
the wrapping paper.
I've really gotten in touch with
my feminine side enough today.
오늘 여자 역할은
이걸로 충분한 것 같아
이거 두 개만 더 만들면
레즈비언 커플 되겠다
In fact, we're two sachets away
from becoming a lesbian couple.
This has been a girlie day.
You're right. I'm sorry.
오늘 자기 너무 무리했지?
알았어, 미안해
괜찮아, 이제 사나이들
놀이로 기분 풀어야지
I just feel like I need
to be in a "guy" place...
do kind of a "man" thing.
그래, 조이한테 가봐
You go over to Joey's and...
가서 맥주 들이붓고
마구 때려 부셔
drink some beer and
hammer up some dry wall.
When guys hang out, they don't just
drink beer and hammer up dry wall.
남자들이 늘 맥주나 마시고
때려부수는 건 아냐
When girls hang out, we don't have
pillow fights in our underwear.
여자들도 늘 속옷바람으로
베개싸움 하는 건 아니지
I'm sorry. We do.
미안, 여자들은 그래
내가 왜 그런 말을 했지?
I don't know why I said that.
너 왔냐?
Hey, Chandler.
Come on in.
We're knitting potholders.
들어와, 화분받침 뜨고 있어
No, thanks, Josephine.
됐다, 조세핀
Ross, I was wondering if..
야, 너 혹시...
Oh, my God! Where are all the men?
환장하겠네
사내들 다 어디 갔어?
안녕하세요, 부장님
-Hi, Kim.
-Hi, Rachel.
그래, 레이첼
어제 제가 드린 말씀 있죠?
그런 일 없었대요
Remember what happened yesterday?
Well, it didn't happen.
You didn't cancel the fabric order?
대만에 옷감 주문한 거
취소 안 했다고?
Okay, two things didn't happen.
네, 그런 일도 없었군요
Remember I told you someone
made out with Ralph Lauren?
회장님이 복사실에서
어쩌고저쩌고 했다는 거
Well, it turns out that's not true.
사실이 아니더라고요
It's not true?
That's interesting.
- 사실이 아냐?
- 네
그거 재미있네
Because I checked. Only one keycard
was used to access the copier...
내가 확인해보니까
어제 점심 때 복사실에서
사용된 유일한 키카드는
yesterday during lunch, and
that keycard belonged to you.
레이첼 거였어
절대 아니에요
설마 제가 그런 짓을
You think I made out with him?
Listen to me...
잘 들어
sleeping with Ralph is not
gonna get you my job.
내 자리를 넘보려고 랄프와
잔다면 그건 큰 계산착오야
I don't want your job. I don't.
부장님 자리를 넘보다뇨
그런 오해는 마세요
전 그런 적 없어요
This is a mistake.
I didn't make out with him.
Nobody made out with him.
I didn't use my keycard yesterday.
아무도 그런 사람 없어요
전 어제 키카드 안 썼어요
키카드 쓰는 법도 몰라요
I don't even know
how to use my keycard.
-Hi, Ralph.
-Hi, Kim.
회장님 나오셨어요?
그래요, 킴
Yeah. Nothing happened.
그래, 아무 일도 없었으면
이 아찔한 긴장감은 뭐지?
You could cut the sexual tension
in here with a knife.
After that, what could I do
except become a chef?
그때부터 꼭 주방장이
되겠다고 다짐했죠
Soon, I hope to open
my own restaurant.
내 레스토랑을 열 거예요
You're a really great listener.
남의 말을 정말 잘 들어주네요
Most guys I go out with,
they talk and talk.
내가 사귀던 남자들은
자기 얘기만 했는데
It's like, "Shut your mouth."
You know?
나중엔 입을 꿰매버리고
싶을 정도라니까요
I've been talking too much.
Why don't we talk about you?
너무 내 얘기만 했네요
그쪽 얘기도 해봐요
어서요, 듣고 싶어요
Come on, I want to know.
Okay. I'm from Long lsland.
좋아요
전 롱아일랜드 출신인데
대학 때문에 뉴욕에 왔죠
I came to the city for college.
I have a 5-year-old son,
and in my spare time...
5살 된 아들이 있고
한가할 땐 첩보소설을 읽어요
I like to read spy novels.
But let's talk more about you.
당신 얘기나 더 듣죠 뭐
그니까 처음에 줄기를
프라이팬에서 약간 그을리면
If you sear the stems of the flowers
first in a frying pan...
꽃이 훨씬 오래간대
your arrangement will
look fresh much longer.
Joey, that is such a great tip!
그거 정말 쓸만한 정보다
Monica, I need to talk
to the girl with the flowers.
모니카, 잠깐 비켜줄래?
꽃 파는 소녀랑 대화 좀 하게
알았어
Okay, but I'm gonna teach you
how to make a bird feeder...
이따가 땅콩버터랑 솔방울로
새 모이 만드는 법 가르쳐줄게
out of a pine cone
and some peanut butter.
I love birds.
나 새 좋아하는데
What is the matter with you?
너 어디 아프냐?
-What?
-You're arranging flowers!
- 뭐가?
- 꽃꽂이가 다 뭐야!
그리고 이건 꽃 시체!
You got dead flowers!
You've got a picture of a baby
dressed like flowers!
꽃처럼 옷 입은
아이 사진도 있네!
This is not Joey!
이건 조이가 아냐
Look, I am still Joey, okay?
진정해, 난 그대로야
Flowers, they're just nice to look at.
꽃이 어때서 그래
보기 좋잖아
저 사진은 유명한
작가가 찍었어
And that happens to be a picture
by a famous artist of a famous baby.
아이도 유명하고
You're turning into a woman.
여자로 변해가는구나
No, I'm not.
말도 안 돼
Why would you say that?
That's just mean.
그런 말은 너무 심하잖니
Now I've upset you? What did I say?
상처받았냐?
내가 뭐랬는데?
It's not what you said.
It's the way you said it.
어떻게 말하느냐가 문제지
Oh, my God!
엄마야!
I'm a woman!
난 여자다!
So now she thinks that I made out
with him to get her job.
글쎄 자기 자리를 넘보려고
랄프랑 키스했다는 거야
-Why didn't you just tell the truth?
-I did.
사실대로 얘기하지
얘기했는데
사환이랑 회장을 혼동하는
바보가 어디 있냐더라
She doesn't think anyone would confuse
Kenny the copy guy with Ralph Lauren.
What if Kenny were the real brains
behind the whole company?
케니가 회사를 조종하는
막후세력이라면 어쩔래
What if Kenny hired that Ralph guy
to be the pretty front man, huh?
랄프가 고용된 얼굴마담이란
생각은 전혀 안 해봤대?
Did she ever think of that?
You were with Kenny today.
너 오늘 케니 만났구나
Just for a second.
그냥 잠깐
- 난 어떡하지?
- 그야...
Phoebe, what am I gonna do?
랄프 로렌하고
자는 수밖에 없다
The only thing you can do.
Sleep with him.
I'm not gonna sleep with him.
I mean, I could, but I wouldn't.
어떻게 랄프 로렌하고 자
뭐 능력은 되지만
내키지 않아
그럼 케니하고 자라
Sleep with Kenny.
- 그게 무슨 도움이 돼?
- 물론 되지
-That wouldn't help me.
-Oh, yes, it would.
I've had a really good time tonight.
오늘 정말 즐거웠어요
I rarely connect with someone
this much on the first date.
처음 만난 사람한테
끌리는 경우는 드문데
저도요
Me neither.
즐거운 시간이었어요
I've had a really
good time too, you know.
Are you gonna eat that bread?
그 빵 먹을 건가요?
I just like the smell.
그냥 냄새가 좋아서
You make me laugh.
재미있네요
Would you like to move to the couch?
저쪽 소파로 갈래요?
Maybe I'll just turn down
the lights a little?
조명을 약간 어둡게 할까요?
How about all the way?
그냥 꺼버리죠 뭐
알았어요
Okay.
Wow, cool poster.
포스터 멋지네요
Or should I say, "groovy poster"?
죽이는 포스터라고 해야 하나?
So...
근데...
where were we?
어디까지 얘기했죠?
Are those your teeth?
그거 진짜 이예요?
저런...
You can see them, huh?
이게 보이는군요
네, 너무 밝아요
Yes. They're insanely white.
당신을 위해 준비한 건데
I did that for you.
What's the matter with you?
대체 어떻게 한 거죠?
내가 어쨌다고, 1999년에
적외선조명을 쓰는 사람이
What's the matter with me?
You've got a black light. It's 1999!
부장님, 안녕하세요
Oh, good. Kim, hi.
Hi, Rachel. I wanted to ask you, have
you seen the new Ralph Lauren sheets?
안녕, 레이첼
참, 궁금한 게 있는데 새로 나온
랄프 로렌 침대보 봤어?
What am I thinking?
Of course you have.
내 정신 좀 보게
물론 봤겠지
네, 좋아요
Okay, look.
I'm sorry that I lied to you before.
거짓말해서 정말 죄송해요
부장님이 옳았어요
You were right. Ralph and I were
an item, but we're not anymore.
회장님과 잠깐 사귀었어요
하지만 지금은 아니에요
Oh, really?
그래?
Yeah, he dumped me.
네, 버림받았어요
He said, "Rachel, I can't do this.
그러더군요
'레이첼, 더는 안 되겠어'
Even though you're a very, very...
'비록 당신은 너무, 너무
너무 아름다운 여인이지만'
very beautiful woman...
I can't do this.
I'm married and I'm sorry."
'이럴 순 없어
난 결혼한 몸이야, 미안해'
But he said,
"And you will never get promoted...
이유는 모르겠지만
이런 말도 했어요
'당신은 승진 못해'
especially not above Kim,
who is an integral cog...
'회사의 핵심세력인 킴을
늘 윗사람으로 모시도록'
in the Ralph Lauren machine."
You expect me to believe..
날더러 그 말을 믿으라고?
- 안녕하세요, 회장님
- 그래요, 킴
-Hi, Ralph.
-Hi, Kim.
Oh, my God.
세상에, 저렇게 싸늘한 시선은
처음이야, 자길 진짜 싫어하네
He gave you the coldest look I've
ever seen. It's like he hates you!
Then it is true!
그럼 사실이구나
Of course it's true.
And it hurts so bad.
물론 사실이죠
너무 가슴 아파요
Oh, honey, come here.
자, 이리 와
괜찮아질 거야
Oh, it'll be okay.
We've all been there.
우리도 다 겪은 일이니까
부장님도 회장님이랑?
You and Ralph?
Kenny the copy boy.
복사실 사환 케니하고
- 나 왔어요
- 그래요
우리 얘기 좀 합시다
-I need to talk to you.
-What's the matter? You upset?
왜 그래요? 화났어요?
Would you like me to get
a pint of ice cream and two spoons?
아이스크림 좀 사올까요?
아뇨, 그거 하지 마요
아이스크림은 됐어요
No, no, no ice cream. Look....
미안하지만 여성스런
물건은 치워야겠어요
We gotta get rid of all
this girlie stuff in here.
I gotta be a man!
사내답게 살고 싶어요
The living room has to
remain a guy place, okay?
알았죠? 거실은
남자의 공간이에요
그렇게 꾸밀 거예요
That's the way it has to be.
I'll just put it all in my room.
- 그럼 내 방으로 옮기죠 뭐
- 좋아요
Good. Great.
잘됐군요, 어쨌든
이해해줘서 고마워요
Thanks for being so understanding.
I didn't want to make
a big deal out of this.
서로 웃으면서
해결하는 게 좋죠
But you could put the picture
of the famous baby in my room.
저 유명한 아기 사진은
내 방에 걸어도 돼요
I mean, if you want to.
원한다면요
Okay.
그래요
- 또 물뿌리개 그림도
- 좋아요
And maybe the watering can there.
Sure.
And a couple of these
little tiny boxes.
이 조그만 박스 몇 개도
Joey, do you want me to put
it all in your room?
조이, 다 그쪽 방으로
옮길까요?
Okay.
그러죠 뭐